Guide to the Pauline Bart papers, 1925-2008 and undated, bulk 1969-1995 RL.10069
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Research Files Series, 1961-1995; undated; 4
  - Rape Avoidance Research Subseries, 1974-1990; undated
    - Police and O, 1974; 1 folders (Box 56)
    - Pre-test info, 1977; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Previous grant on "Avoiding Rape" for reference, 1976; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Questionnaire/Pilot Study, 1976; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Rape avoidance research, 1979-1990; undated; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Rape data, undated; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Rape notes/research (handwritten), undated; 1 folders (Box 57)
    - Rape Questionnaires, 1974; 15 folders (Box 57-59)
    - Rape surveys and research reports, undated; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Research, undated; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Respondents' description of mother, undated; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - SACP protocols and other, undated; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Safe complete, 1977-1987; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Safe forms, undated; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Second year grant materials, 1978; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Sex assault documentation checklist, 1988; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Surveillance committee, undated; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - "Who Is Rapist", 1974 (Box 60)
      Contains a letter from a survivor of incestuous sexual assault describing her attacker's personality.
    - Victim report Spanish, undated; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Women who had multiple experiences, undated; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Loose notes on rape avoidance study, undated; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Loose papers on rape avoidance study, undated; 1 folders (Box 60)
    - Sheets of statistics, 1983; 3 folders (Box 61)
    - Strategies- statistical analysis, 1979; 3 folders (Box 61-62)
    - Viva Output on Avoiding Rape, 1975; 1 folders (Box 62)
  - Depression Study Subseries, 1964
    The Depression Study Subseries contains materials related to the study that Bart conducted in pursuit of her dissertation, "Depression in Middle-Aged Women." In the study, Bart interviewed women admitted to the University of California at Los Angeles's Neuropsychiatric Institute and Gateways Hospital and Mental Health Center for depression. Papers include interview transcripts, notes, a research proposal, and other materials.
    - Age and Sex Admissions by Gateways, 1964; 1 folders (Box 63)
    - Content analysis of interviews, 1964; 1 folders (Box 63)
    - Gateways inteview materials, 1964; 1 folders (Box 63)
    - Gateways interviews, 1964; 7 folders (Box 63)
    - NPI interviews, 1964; 7 folders (Box 63)
    - NPI- P&N names and those pulled, 1964; 1 folders (Box 63)
    - Proposal and supplementary materials, 1964; 1 folders (Box 63)
    - Transcription of notes on interviews, 1964; 1 folders (Box 63)
  - Other Research Files Subseries, 1961-1995; undated
    The Other Research Files Subseries contains subject files on various topics related to feminism, women's health, psychology and other subjects. Topics include pornography, depression, violence against women, the Illinois sexual assault statute, feminism, rape, homosexuality, and other subjects. Papers tend to consist largely of clippings and notes on these subjects, with occasional correspondence and other materials.
    - Abortion, 1973; 1988; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Loose papers on abortion, 1970-1985; undated; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Academic women, undated; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Acquaintance rape, undated; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Acquaintance rape and sexual assault program, 1987; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - The adaptive role of depression in health and disease, 1970; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Aging, 1963-1976; 2 folders (Box 64)
    - Research on aging, 1983-1986; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - AIDS, undated; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Airline stewardesses, 1971-1972; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Alcoholism, 1976; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Ann Landers re: rape, undated; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Anti-rape groups, 1975-1978; 1 folders (Box 64)
    - Appendix: Med. Student social network index, undated; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Are sex roles changing housework schedules, undated; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Arlene Wilson folder, undated; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Articles by Patricia A. Resick, 1979-1986; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - ASA, undated; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - ASA Footnotes, 1986-1988; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Audre Lorde, undated; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - AWP Jewish, 1989; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Baby M/S, 1987; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Bardwick, 1971; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Battered Data Syndrome materials, 1978; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Battered husbands, 1978; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Battered women, 1985-1994; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Batya Weinbaum's story re: rape, 1979; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Becker Mary Fetal Vulnerability, 1986; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Behavior Today newsletters, 1977-1978; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Behavioral vulnerability and the menstrual cycle, 1976; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Bernard Wife Role, undated; 1 folders (Box 65)
    - Bibliographies: Women and Health, 1976-1978; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - A Biosocial Perspective on Parenting, undated; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Books on sexism in psychology, undated; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Loose papers on breast cancer, 1986-1994; undated; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Notes on brutal beatings, undated; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Burgess book, undated; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Carroll Smith Rosenberg, 1985; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Catherine MacKinnon: Feminist Theory paper, 1982; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Cecelia Kitzinger, 1992; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Child development, 1952-1971; undated; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Loose papers on child maltreatment, 1974-1979; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Child sex abuse cases, 1990; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Child sexual assault, 1983-1995; undated; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Children in the welfare state, 1982; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Chinese SSH, 1980; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Commentary on Phyllis Chesler's Women and Madness, 1986; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Computer consultants, undated; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Consultation agreements, 1979; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Consultation with Rosabeth Kanter, undated; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Consultations, 1978; undated; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Contemporary Sociology Review criticism, 1986; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Loose papers on contraceptives, 1975; 1 folders (Box 66)
    - Correspondence with rapists or facsimile, 1979; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Criminal court article (Tribune), 1987-1989; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Criminology, undated; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Dalkon Shield, 1976; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Dan research, 1991; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Data available from the Criminal Justice Archive, 1981; undated; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Day care, 1971; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Definition of avoidance, 1978; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - The Depressed Woman, Weissman and Paykel, 1974; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Loose papers on depression, 1974-1983; undated; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - DES, undated; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Diana Scully, 1978-1983; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Divorced men copy 1, 1970; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Divorced Men and Their Roles, undated; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Dixon M., 1969; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Domestic violence (general), undated; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Domestic violence Byrne, undated; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Dove Counterbalance, 1969; undated; 1 folders (Box 67)
    - Drafts of Childhood Memories by Manya Pruzhanskaya Lackow, 1984; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - DSM, undated; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - DSM III Review, 1985; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - Dworkin, 1978; undated; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - Effects of rape, undated; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - Equal Rights Amendment, 1970; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - Ethical Issues in Delivering Discoveries, undated; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - Exploratory Study of Assault Outcomes- Bureau of Social Science Research, undated; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - Father of out of wedlock child, 1971; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - Feminism, 1987; undated; 1 folders (Box 68)
    - Loose papers on feminism, 1979-2002; undated; 3 folders (Box 68)
    - Feminist Sociology articles, reviews, 1969-1974; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Feminist Theory- Artemis March, 1978; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Feminist Therapy, 1973-1975; undated; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - For Better Times: ICADV, 1991-1993; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - For NOW, 1976; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Foucault on rape, 1981; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Frank E. Saal- Men's Perspectives of Women's Reactions, undated; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Freud on Women, 1970; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Gail E. Wyatt, 1986; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Gender and language, 1990; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Gender and society, 1983-1987; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Gender and Society Journal, 1989; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Gloria L., undated; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Grants awarded for rape research studies, 1976-1980; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Guidelines, 1974-1975; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Haggadah, undated; 1 folders (Box 69)
    - Handwritten notes, undated; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Helena Lopata, 1981; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Herman [incest], 1981; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - History of SWS Women's Caucus, undated; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - History of violence against women, undated; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Homstrom and Burgess: rape, 1979-1983; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Homosexuality, 1961-1975; undated; 2 folders (Box 70)
    - Hong Chen- Mental Health in China, 1988; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Housewives, undated; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - ICADV battered women questionnaire, undated; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - ICASA Coalition commentary, 1987-1988; 1 folders (Box 70)
    - Illinois Coalition Against Sexual Assault (ICASA), 1986-1988; 1 folders (Box 71)
    - Illinois Commission on the Status of Women, 1983-1984; 1 folders (Box 71)
    - Illinois Criminal Sexual Assault Act, 1983; 1 folders (Box 71)
    - Illinois legal information, 1983-1987; undated; 1 folders (Box 71)
    - Illinois sexual assault investigation notes, 1988; undated; 1 folders (Box 71)
    - Illinois sexual assault statute, 1985-1991; 2 folders (Box 71)
    - Notes on Illinois Sexual Assault Statute, undated; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Loose papers on incest, 1977-1981; undated; 1 folders (Box 71)
    - Incest articles, undated; 1 folders (Box 71)
    - Incest/child abuse, 1980-1984; undated; 1 folders (Box 71)
    - Institute for Women's Policy Research- Pearl Hartmanu, 1 folders (Box 72)
    - International Women's Club of Kyoto monthly newsletter, vol. 2, no. 6, undated; 1 folders (Box 72)
    - Interview with Phyllis Chesler, undated; 1 folders (Box 72)
    - Interviews with medical professionals attacked by patients, undated; 1 folders (Box 72)
    - Is Anatomy Destiny? ASA, 1973-1976; 1 folders (Box 72)
    - Israel, 1970-1971; 1 folders (Box 72)
    - Israel OB, 1976; 1 folders (Box 72)
    - Jean L. Blumer, 1973; 1 folders (Box 72)
    - Jeffners Rape, 1981; 1 folders (Box 72)
    - Loose papers on Jewish women, undated; 1 folders (Box 72)
    - Jews and Blacks, 1990-1994; 1 folders (Box 72)
    - Joe Pleck, 1972-1973; 1 folders (Box 72)
    - Joint Committee on the Status of Women, 1976; 1 folders (Box 72)
    - July 30 1918 to Odessa August and September 1918, undated; 1 folders (Box 72)
    - Kennedy-Smith case newsclippings, 1991; 1 folders (Box 72)
    - Kim Scheppele, 1979; 1 folders (Box 72)
    - L.A. Protocol for the Treatment of Rape, 1986; 1 folders (Box 72)
    - Labor force, 1974; undated; 1 folders (Box 72)
    - Lackow- in the Russian Gymnasia, undated; 1 folders (Box 73)
    - Lackow- undated draft, 1 folders (Box 73)
    - Lahey C. Surrogacy, 1987; 1 folders (Box 73)
    - Laws on equality for women, 1970-1972; 1 folders (Box 73)
    - Lesbians, undated; 1 folders (Box 73)
    - Loose papers on lesbians, 1982-1993; undated; 1 folders (Box 73)
    - Love Canal, undated; 1 folders (Box 73)
    - MacKinnon, 1987; 1 folders (Box 73)
    - Mao Tse-tung, Women, and Suicide in the May Fourth Era, undated; 1 folders (Box 73)
    - Published commentary on Mao and Meade, 1983; undated; 1 folders (Box 73)
    - Mapplethorpe, 1990; 1 folders (Box 73)
    - Marcia Westkott- Female Relationality and the Idealized Self, undated draft, 1 folders (Box 73)
    - Marital Rape, 1979; undated; 1 folders (Box 73)
    - Marlene, undated; 1 folders (Box 73)
    - Mary Becker, undated; 1 folders (Box 73)
    - Mary Howell, 1973-1975; undated; 2 folders (Box 73-74)
    - Med Schools, undated; 1 folders (Box 74)
    - Med clinic, 1973-1976; undated; 1 folders (Box 74)
    - Media and women, 1972; 1 folders (Box 74)
    - Medical Industrial Complex, undated; 1 folders (Box 74)
    - Medical sociology, 1961-1969; 1 folders (Box 74)
    - Medical student lectures on rape and AB, 1983; undated; 1 folders (Box 74)
    - Menopause, 1976-1978; undated; 2 folders (Box 74)
    - Loose papers on menopause, undated; 1 folders (Box 75)
    - Menstruation, 1977; undated; 1 folders (Box 75)
    - Meyer- Ideology re: women in american history; also novels re: women, undated; 1 folders (Box 75)
    - Michael Reese, 1989; 1 folders (Box 75)
    - Minority report- Illinois commission on women, 1983-1984; 1 folders (Box 75)
    - Most Important, undated; 1 folders (Box 75)
    - Motherhood, 1976-1982; undated; 1 folders (Box 75)
    - Mothers, 1971; undated; 1 folders (Box 75)
    - Muslim women course for med students, undated; 1 folders (Box 75)
    - My Brief Career as a Femme, undated; 1 folders (Box 75)
    - Myth of a Value-Free Psychotherapy, undated; 1 folders (Box 75)
    - Naomi Weisstein, 1969; 1 folders (Box 76)
    - National Science Foundation grant funding, undated; 1 folders (Box 76)
    - NCASA News, 1987; 1 folders (Box 76)
    - NCHS Vital Statistics, 1980-1982; 1 folders (Box 76)
    - Network News, 1985; 1 folders (Box 76)
    - New Bedford rape file, 1984; 1 folders (Box 76)
    - Miscellaneous newsletters, 1971-1995; 2 folders (Box 76)
    - Niles Newton, 1968; 1 folders (Box 76)
    - Non-Academic women, 1970; undated; 1 folders (Box 76)
    - Miscellaneous notes, undated; 2 folders (Box 76-77)
    - Miscellaneous notes on cases, undated; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Nursing, undated; 1 folders (Box 77)
    - Nutrition (articles), undated; 1 folders (Box 77)
    - OB Gyne psychosomatic, undated; 1 folders (Box 77)
    - Obscene phone calls, 1988; 1 folders (Box 77)
    - Odeon Film Catalog, 1975; 1 folders (Box 77)
    - Office of Women's Affairs, 1991; 1 folders (Box 77)
    - Older women's health care, 1986-1989; 1 folders (Box 77)
    - Pager response instructions, undated; 1 folders (Box 77)
    - Pamphlets, undated; 1 folders (Box 77)
    - Loose papers on parenting, undated; 1 folders (Box 77)
    - Pat Miller, 1979; 1 folders (Box 77)
    - Patricia Townsend- Never is Forever, undated; 1 folders (Box 77)
    - People of Illinois v. John Haywood, 1986; 1 folders (Box 77)
    - People of Illinois v. Kevin Whitecotton, 1986; 1 folders (Box 77)
    - Personality as a predictor of outcome of treatment of depression, 1976; 1 folders (Box 77)
    - Peter's data, undated; 1 folders (Box 77)
    - Pildes, undated; 1 folders (Box 77)
    - Playboy, 1971-1985; 1 folders (Box 77)
    - Pleck papers, 1973-1977; 1 folders (Box 77)
    - Pornography, 1982-1987; undated; 2 folders (Box 77-78)
    - Loose papers on pornography, 1988-1994; undated; 2 folders (Box 78)
    - Pornography presentation, undated; 1 folders (Box 78)
    - Pornography and sexual assault survey, 1975-1985; undated; 1 folders (Box 78)
    - Prof. Bennett Berger file, 1983-1984; 1 folders (Box 78)
    - Prostitution, 1983; 1 folders (Box 78)
    - Loose papers on prostitution, 1986; 1 folders (Box 78)
    - Psychology today responses, 1969; 1 folders (Box 78)
    - Publications info, 1977; 1 folders (Box 78)
    - Queen's Bench Foundation, Carol Marks, Ph.D., undated; 1 folders (Box 78)
    - Queen's Bench Forms, 1976; 1 folders (Box 78)
    - R. Blumberg, 1973; 1 folders (Box 78)
    - Loose papers on racism, undated; 1 folders (Box 78)
    - Rape, 1980; undated; 1 folders (Box 79)
    - Loose papers on rape, 1975-1991; undated; 7 folders (Box 79-80)
    - Loose handwritten notes on rape, undated; 1 folders (Box 80)
    - Rape avoidance, 1984; undated; 1 folders (Box 80)
    - Rape cross cultural, 1979; 1 folders (Box 80)
    - Rape disposition of case, undated; 1 folders (Box 80)
    - Rape- Gordon and Riger, 1978; 2 folders (Box 80)
    - Rape historical, undated; 1 folders (Box 80)
    - Rape homicides, 1981; 1 folders (Box 80)
    - Rape in Israel, undated; 1 folders (Box 80)
    - Rape laws- miscellaneous papers, undated; 1 folders (Box 80)
    - Rape laws correspondence regarding, 1974-1979; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Rape letters regarding, 1979; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Rape in marriage, 1978-1982; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Rape and murder, 1985; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Rape notes, undated; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Rape: organizing against it, ISIS, 1979; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Rape papers from ACJS, 1990; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Rape research, presentations, 1975-1976; undated; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Rape resistance, 1985-1986; 1 folders (Box 81)
    - Rape "response" news, 1984; undated; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Rape undocumented women, 1986; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Reference cards, undated; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Reports on minority sexual harassment/rape, 1989-1991; undated; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Reproductive technology, 1984; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Research notes, undated; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Reskin- code sheet (NSF), 1981; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Resolutions: NCSA pornography, lingerie, 1986; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Respondent 11 session 1, undated; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Response (journal), 1982-1987; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Response to Family Violence and Sexual Assault, 1982; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Role of Daughters healthcare book draft, undated; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Rowland Judy, undated; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - RVA, 1983; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Sacramento porn, 1982-1983; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Sandy Alcorn, 1982; 1 folders (Box 82)
    - Scully paper, 1977; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Self help, 1978; undated; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Sex abuse of children, undated; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Sex and friendship chapters, undated; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Sex roles, 1971; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Loose papers on sex roles, 1970s; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Loose papers on sexual assault cases, 1986; undated; 1 folders (Box 83)
    - Sexual harassment, 1980-1991; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Sexuality and the law, undated; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Shulamit Reinharz, 1987; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Notes on sisterhood, undated; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Snow and Phillips- From Institution to Impulse, 1981; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Socialization, 1970; undated; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Loose papers on sociology, undated; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Sophia, 1987-1988; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Spokeswoman Newsletter, 1972-1974; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Stopping Rape, 1988; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Stranger rape, undated; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - M. Strauss, 1989; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Suicidal, 1991; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Suicide, 1979-1990; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Suicide Review Board, 1991; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Suicide Review Committee, 1983-1990; 1 folders (Box 84)
    - Tapes from Europe, undated; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - USSR, rape, 1990-1991; undated; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Violence against women, 1982-1987; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Loose papers on violence against women, 1976-1990; undated; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Washington state sexual assault, 1984-1986; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Women: a Guide to Sources of Information, 1976; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Women and aging, 1982-1989; 2 folders (Box 85)
    - Loose papers on women and aging, undated; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Women and education plus some women's studies, 1973; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Women in Health: an Annotated Bibliography, undated; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Women and health care, 1973; 1 folders (Box 85)
    - Women and health care articles, 1976-1977; undated; 1 folders (Box 86)
    - Women and the law, 1983; 1 folders (Box 86)
    - Women and medicine, 1978-1981; undated; 1 folders (Box 86)
    - Women in prison, undated; 1 folders (Box 86)
    - Women violence articles, undated; 1 folders (Box 86)
    - Women's history, 1968-1975; undated; 2 folders (Box 86)
    - Women's History Archives UICC, undated; 1 folders (Box 62)
    - Working Women- Department of Labor, 1966-1970; undated; 1 folders (Box 86)
    - World of Our Mothers, undated; 1 folders (Box 87)
    - X-Cultural material, undated; 1 folders (Box 87)
    - Loose papers, miscellaneous, 1962-1984; undated; 6 folders (Box 87)
- Audiotapes Series, 1974-1994; undated; 1
  Box 90 is closed to researchers until 2039.
  The Audiotapes series contains recordings of talks given by Bart, conference sessions, presentations, interviews, and classes conducted at the University of Illinois at Chicago. Also included are recordings of 9 interviews with members of the Jane Collective (see box 90).
  - Dr. Goldberg- Sexuality Tapes 1 and 2; Dr. Segtauer, 1974 December 18; 1
    - Original 1/4-inch (Box 88, Artifact-box RL10069-RR-0001)
  - Dr. Harting, Straussman, Chicago Med, undated; 2
    - Original 1/4-inch (Box 88, Audio-reel RL10069-RR-0002)
  - #80 IV Finish, undated; 3
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0001)
  - Neil [illegible] porn, undated; 4
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0002)
  - Ntozake Shange, 1983 April 11; 5
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0003)
  - Chicago Med Students, 1974 July 11; 6
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0004)
  - Dr. Goldberg Sexuality Tape, 1974 December 18; 7
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0005)
  - Negative discussion of rape papers, undated; 8
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0006)
  - Women Music [illegible], undated; 9
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0007)
  - Dr. Harting Sexuality - Rush, 1974 December 19; 10
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0008)
  - Denise Sex Ed at Harvard, undated; 11
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0009)
  - Kitty MacKinnon, undated; 12
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0010)
  - Sexuality Alouf and Mandel, 1974 December 9; 13
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0011)
  - Kitty Sexual Harrassment NOW, undated; 14
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0012)
  - Pornography, undated; 15
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0013)
  - Paper IWY, undated; 16
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0014)
  - Kitty MacKinnon/Cassie Statuto & RB, undated; 17
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0015)
  - Straussman Chicago Med, undated; 18
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0016)
  - Dr. Segtauer, undated; 19
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0017)
  - JOHH Krenger 74, 1974; 20
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0018)
  - Med Students Chicago, 1974 July 11; 21
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0019)
  - [title illegible], undated; 22
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0020)
  - Women's World Israel Rape Session Scully Bart Ames [illegible] and Esther Elar, undated; 23
    - Original audiocassette (Box 89, Audio-cassette RL10069-CS-0021)
  - Women in Science Study Group, 1973 December; 24